export const questionList = [{
    question: 'Who was the first human to travel into space?',
    answer: 'Yuri Gagarin (USSR, 1961)',
}, {
    question: 'What was the name of the first woman in space?',
    answer: 'Valentina Tereshkova (USSR, 1963)'
}, {
    question: 'Which Apollo mission landed the first humans on the Moon?',
    answer: 'Apollo 11 (1969)'
},  {
    question: 'Who became the first space tourist to visit the International Space Station (ISS) in 2001?',
    answer: 'Dennis Tito'
}, {
    question: 'What is the name of NASAâ€™s rover that landed on Mars in February 2021?',
    answer: 'Perseverance'
}, {
    question: 'Which space telescope, launched in 1990, revolutionized astronomy with its deep-space images?',
    answer: 'Hubble Space Telescope'
}, {
    question: 'Which company launched the first commercially built spacecraft to dock with the ISS in 2012?',
    answer: 'SpaceX (Dragon spacecraft)'
}, {
    question: 'What is the farthest human-made object from Earth?',
    answer: 'Voyager 1 (launched in 1977)'
}, {
    question: 'What was the name of the first animal sent into orbit (1957)?',
    answer: 'Laika (a Soviet space dog)'
}, {
    question: 'Which planet in our solar system has the most moons (as of 2023)?',
    answer: 'Saturn (146 confirmed moons)'
}]